RAMYA ILAYARAJA

NehruStreet,

ramprithu@gmail.com

#4,

Nilamangai Nagar, Adambakkam, Chennai 600088. Phone: 9962807909(M) 044 - 43526738

Objective:

Despite being a radiographer, I am more inclined towards teaching and handling young children. I have close to 2 years of experience as a Therapy Assistant. I am looking forward to use my experience and communication skills to excel in the field of teaching. I am also currently pursuing Physics, bachelor's degree.

Expertise/Strengths:

- ✓ Excellent Communication, presentation, Interpersonal, learning, analytical and logical skills matched with ability to manage stress and time efficiently
- ✓ Passionate about learning new technologies and a very quick learner
- ✓ Great people person and love the challenge of working at a faster pace

Accomplishments:

- ✓ Completed Diploma in MS Office and Internet
- ✓ Completed basic proficiency (Madhyama) in Hindi

Technical skills:

- ✓ Operating System: Windows XP, windows 7 basic, Win 8, 10
- ✓ Packages: MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint

Education:

Diploma in X-ray Technician (2011-2013) from Annai Theresa Institute of Paramedical Technology, Chennai.

B.Sc Physics (2017 – 2020) (Distant Mode)

Work Experience:

April 2014 – till date

Teacher, Coordinator & Therapy Assistant, Admin Manager – Sri Saii Child Development Centre, Adambakkam, Chennai.

Responsibilities:

- ✓ Managing patients' register
- ✓ Scheduling appointments
- ✓ Engaging children in group therapy sessions

- ✓ Conducting play therapy sessions for children
- ✓ Assisting in report preparation
- ✓ Coordinating with other Therapists on scheduling sessions

April 2013 - March 2014

Handling mammogram cases on appointment at Sri Balaji Medical College and hospital, Chrompet, Chennai.

March 2012 - March 2013

Radiographer, Sri Balaji Medical College and hospital, Chrompet, Chennai.

Responsible for handling cases for Digital X-Ray, mammogram in $800\,\mathrm{MA}$, $500\,\mathrm{MA}$ X-Ray machines.

In – Plant Training:

December 2011-february 2012

Undergone Training in X-Ray at V seshiah Diabetic Research Institute Amjikarai, chennai.

Personal Information:

Father's Name : S. Ragunathan.

Date of Birth : 27thDecember 1987

Age : 30

Communication and Permanent address:#4, Nehru Street, Nilamangai nagar,

Adambakkam, Chennai-88.

Declaration:

I hereby confirm that all the above furnished information is completely true to my conscience.

Date: 30.04.2018

Place: Chennai Ramya Ilayaraja.